[ED.
Congratulations on your Maika purchase!
Thank you very much.
Cheers.
It's kind of weird, though. There's not much of a ratio.
Oh well, it's a girl's party today.
So this time, as a special edition of Tomita's car-buying project, we held a party to congratulate Ms. Suzuka on her purchase of a maika.
Thank you! I'm so glad!
You're throwing me a party when I buy a car.
We were there last time... and she really bought it.
I want to sign the contract and wear the Cheki Hunter today.
What kind of car did you buy? Can I show you? Sure.
It's so cool!
Is it green? It's a color called jungle green.
It's like this. Isn't it pretty? It's cute.
It's cute. It looks good on you. Really? I like rugged cars like this.
I really liked the ride.
I thought it might be hard to get in if you're looking at it from above, but it was totally comfortable.
Where would you like to go in this car?
But recently I've been working in Sanriku, so I'd like to go to Sanriku.
I want to go to Iwate and Miyagi. I want to go to Tohoku.
This car is easy to drive on snowy and gravel roads.
I'll go to Tohoku. I'll go to the mountains.
I can go over the mountains... Jungle Green
Only Jungle Green is fun!
What's the driving school like?
I went to a driving school in Tokyo.
I went to a driving school in Tokyo, but I didn't really think about my schedule or when I was going to school.
After rehearsals for the tour, I guess.
Was it like that? I had to have it.
And it was very last minute. It was due in a year or something.
But we finished shooting about three days before.
It's dangerous, right? Thank God it was so last-minute.
I was so busy.
So who do you want to be the first to get in this car?
I was hoping to pick up someone reliable.
I was thinking maybe two people who can operate the navigation system.
Maybe two people. Maybe two.
Are you sure they're in the car?
But wouldn't it be great if there were two people in the passenger seat?
Really?
You know how to operate this thing, right?
I'm more of a get in, get in the passenger seat, operate the car type of guy.
Really?
Are you sure you're okay with that?
I don't know.
Are you good with roads? Maps?
I'll be in the back and you in the passenger seat.
That's great, that's great.
I'd love to take anyone who wants to go.
I'd love to take you guys on a road trip sometime.
I'd love to.
You know how you said we need to get car insurance?
You've both been in Sonny Sonpo's commercials.
Do you know much about it?
Not really.
But I know a little bit.
This is what I've been studying.
They're in a commercial.
I see them all the time.
I'm so happy to see you two in a circle in a commercial
I'm happy to see you two in a circle in a commercial.
Should I get car insurance?
There are two types of car insurance.
So, does that mean I should get auto insurance?
Self-insured motorist insurance is designed to help victims of accidents.
If you cause injury to the other party...
It only covers accidents involving bodily injury.
And there's a cap on the amount of money that can be paid.
If the amount of compensation is too high
If the amount of compensation is too high, there is a possibility that the insurance company will not be able to pay it.
It depends on the size of the accident.
If you damage the other party's car
or you are injured If you are injured or your car is damaged
If you are injured or your car is damaged
You are not covered by your own insurance.
That's a problem, isn't it?
You can set up a wide range of coverage
You may also want to purchase an optional auto insurance policy
It might be safer
It's better to have car insurance
We also feel safer
We feel safer when we know that others have car insurance
I feel safer and we feel safer too
Now that you understand the importance of car insurance
Yes, thank you very much
Insurance quiz
If you are driving and hit someone's fence or
If you hit or break someone's fence
your car insurance will cover the cost of repairing the fence.
But as you said before
You are covered for injuries, accidents, and so on.
I'm just saying it's a broad coverage.
I think it's covered.
Bing bong!
Yes!
That's right!
That was embarrassing.
It was embarrassing.
Big Buddha Liability Insurance will cover the cost of repairs.
Big Buddha Liability Insurance
Then there could be a lot more than just soldiers.
Peace of mind
Now let's go to the second question
If it rains today and my car is damaged, is it covered?
It's a natural disaster, so it's hard to say.
And it's not an object.
It's not a thing, and it's covered.
You already looked like you'd be covered from the start.
You need to get a new car insurance policy. I need to get a new kind of car insurance.
I see.
So you're covered for natural disasters, too?
That's great.
They do.
Even today?
I'm so glad.
That's great.
It's a relief, really.
By the way, how much does car insurance cost?
For example, it depends on the purpose of use of the car, the range of drivers covered, the age requirement, and so on.
The premiums seem to change depending on the plan you want.
It also depends on the age of the driver?
Yes, it does.
So you can find a plan that suits your daily life.
How do I choose a plan?
With Sony Sompo, you can consult with a person in charge of the plan through chat or phone call.
So I think it will be very helpful for a newcomer like Suzu.
I think it's very reassuring.
It's hard to know what's good for you if it's your first time.
If it's your first time, it's important to ask for advice.
I appreciate that you can chat with them.
I'm going to search for it later.
By all means, please search!
Where should I go to get car insurance?
You can go to the dealer where you bought your car, or you can go through an agent to get an introduction to auto insurance.
or through an agent.
There are also direct insurance companies like Sony Sompo.
You can make a contract on the Internet from the comfort of your home.
That's very convenient!
After all, when you go somewhere, you may want to ask a few questions.
But if you can do it online, it's very convenient because they are working very hard.
It's not always easy to get in on my schedule.
It's not that hard, so I can do it at a time that's convenient for me.
If you apply online, you get a discount, and you can even apply on your phone.
You can sign up on your phone? Why not a computer?
You get a discount? That's great.
After all, you need car insurance to drive with peace of mind. After all, you need car insurance to drive with peace of mind.
Just by having that kind of insurance, you can go to many places with ease.
I think it's definitely safe for us as well as for our families and fans.
I'm watching the video of Suzu buying a car.
I'm getting worried.
Yes, you're right. I'm definitely going to join.
I'm glad I asked you two.
I've been watching the video of Suzu buying a car.
Thank you very much.
It would have been great to be there.
It's really today.
I was a high angel.
It was expensive. It was really expensive.
I was high.
I got carried away.
I bought a car. What's going to happen now that you're buying a car, Tomita?
What's going to happen now?
I bought it because I feel like I'm done with season 1.
I'm going to customize the interior of the car.
Yes, I'm going to do that.
I also want to do a driving project.
If the three of us were to go for a drive, where would you like to go?
Where would be good?
But you know, Nao's parents live in Osaka.
Osaka is a bit far, but I wonder how long it would take us to get there by car.
I wonder how long it would take if we drove there.
About 5 to 6 hours.
Shall we go?
I want to go.
Then some place with a beautiful night view.
Great. That's great.
We can go to Yokohama or something like that in a flash.
That's true.
Yokohama sounds nice.
Yokohama's nice, isn't it?
Yokohama's nice.
When the three of us go for a drive... When the three of us go for a drive.
I really want to put on some music.
It's a must.
What kind of music do you like to play in the sun?
I don't know.
But I get a little shaky when I listen to heavy music while driving.
I get a little shaky.
I'm scared. I'm still cautious.
I like something a little more subdued.
You don't happen to be calm.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
But it's good.
It's better that way.
What's your favorite song?
What? I don't know.
It's okay.
It's pretty intense.
Maybe a little intense.
It's a little harder than I expected.
It's a little harder than I thought it would be.
I don't know if I'll ever hear that part again.
Oh, she's asleep.
It's a little funny.
That's good.
Thank God they're singing live.
Thank God for live singing.
That's a good idea.
We used to do karaoke in the car.
You can sing in the car and not be embarrassed.
It's fun.
Let's sing while we go.
It'll be fun!
Thank you very much for watching this show.
Please subscribe to the channel and click the "Good" button!
And Sunny Sanpo, too!
Bye bye! a